undercontrolgame.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy policy – Under Control

_Last Update: September 15, 2015_

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the Sites, Game and Services offered by us and regulates how we treat your persona information.

This Privacy Policy is made to provide clarity about the information we collect and how we use it to provide a better gaming experience. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We do follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted, both during transmission and once we receive it. Therefore, while our goal to use commercially acceptable ways to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee it is absolutely secure. Please note that information that you voluntarily make public, or which you disclose by posting comments or inserting of the Content will be publicly available and viewable by others. We do not hold any liability for any information that you voluntarily choose to be public through such and/or other explicit actions.

We only use personal information collected through any of the Sites, Game and Services for the purposes described in the Terms and below in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use your personal information:

a. To respond to your submissions, questions, comments, requests and complaints and provide customer support;

b. To monitor and analyze usage of the Game and trends in order to personalize and improve the Game and experience of our users while using any of the Sites, Game or Services;

c. To provide relevant content, ads and features that match your or other people preferences;

d. To increase functionality and general quality of the Game;

e. To send you confirmations, updates, security alerts and support/administrative messages;

f. For marketing campaigns purposes, including (without limitation) email marketing campaigns.

g. For any other purposes, which we believe are necessary and for which the information is collected.

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through Game or our Services with third parties, except as described in the Terms. For example, we share information as follows:

a. When we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants or court orders;

b. When you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you on the Game that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;

In general, we may request and store following information from you:

a. Your email address;

b. Your first and last names;

c. Your age;

d. Your gender;

e. Your location and time-zone;

f. Your address;

g. Interface display language;

h. You in-game chat messages and history;

i. History of all your actions in the Game;

j. History of your purchase of Virtual Goods;

k. Your messages sent to our Support and history of all inquires;

l. Details from your Facebook™ account which either you or Facebook™ are willing to share with us, including but not limited to: your name, your age and gender, list of friends, location, etc.

In order to make your visits to our Sites as pleasant as possible, we use, like many other companies, cookies and web beacons (collectively, “Data Collection Tools”). These Data Collection Tools automatically track and collect certain technical information that your browser sends to us. This information might include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, the browser type, browser language, Internet service providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, URLs, operating systems, date/time stamps, clickstream data and other similar information. However, this information doesn't identify individual users and we use it exclusively to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user movements around the site as a whole to improve the services provided.

Your Internet browser can be set to reject cookies generally. Note that we recommend you to allow all cookies from our Sites, otherwise some of our Services may work incorrectly and some features may become unavailable.

Your information with limited access rights (including personal information) can only be accessed by our authorized employees or consultants or the concerned group entities that need to have access to this data in order to be able to fulfill their given duties.

Any information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our privacy policy from time to time without prior warning or notification. We strongly advise you to visit this page and read this Privacy Policy every time you access any of the Sites, Game or Services.

This Privacy Policy is the legal part of the Terms of Service, which is published at: [terms](http://undercontrolgame.com/en/terms).
